Angel Martinez

Web Developer

For more than five years as a self-taught developer, I'm constantly learning and perfecting my skill as a developer every day. I enjoy challenges and goals that force me to increase my knowledge and skills. I like to create things with JavaScript/TypeScript technologies that can help people do their chores easiest and faster.

Nava, Mexico
+52 (862) 123 1086
https://angelmtz.dev
@angelmtztrc on GitHub
@angelmtztrc on Twitter
angel.martineztrc@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer @ EDteam

JUL 2021 - PRESENT

My main chores were maintaining a web application built with Next.js and JavaScript, I also collaborated in the development of a static website built Next.js and TypeScript to avoid the overload of pages and requests in the web application.

Full-stack Developer @ Jo Automation Systems

OCT 2019 - PRESENT

I develop and maintain both back-end and front-end projects created with JavaScript/TypeScript technologies.

Freelancer Web Develop @ Self-employed

FEB 2020 - JUL 2021

I've developed websites and small projects for local businesses to help them to start their business in the digital world.

EDUCATION

Universidad Autónoma del Noreste — Software Engineering

JAN 2022 - PRESENT

CBTis No. 239 — Computer Technician

FEB 2018 - JUN 2021

ONLINE EDUCATION

JavaScript Intermediate @ HackerRank

Issued Nov, 2021 - ID 5044b8ebf76b

Reactive RxJS @ Udemy

Issued Aug, 2021 - ID UC-299cd952-de26-4edd-81c8-c067d7639a5b

React - La Guía Completa @ Udemy

Issued Jan, 2021 - ID UC-f22b0079-cd25-426a-b391-24cea8249499

INTERESTS

Contribute to the open-source community.

Develop an open-source library/tool.

Become a Game Developer.

SKILLS / ABILITIES

Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS/SASS, GraphQL Python

Libraries & Frameworks: React.js, Next.js, Redux, React Query, Nest.js, Express.js, Jest, Apollo GraphQL

Tools & Platforms: Git, Vercel, Heroku, Docker, GitHub Actions, Node.js, MongoDB

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native

English - B1